Because honestly, Roe v. Wade, many have said, being repealed was because there is like a fear
that there aren't enough white babies being born. If anything, we need to actually make more brown
babies. But I would never task black women with more s*** to do. Okay, we're very busy.
We've been saving the world for a very long time. You know, we're getting our hair done. We have
things. We're looking for new braiders. We're busy. I think that the task of making more brown babies
should go to somebody else. Like, you know, all the brothers who be like, I don't date black women
because y'all have attitudes. Have I got a job for you? Go find you a Tammy, a Becky, a Hannah. Get
busy. And we can just pass water, you know, keep them hydrated. Like, yeah, because it only takes
one of us to make a brown baby. Put that divide and conquer to good use.
I won't be performing in L.A. anytime soon. Let's sell these out, y'all.